Holly.
Hi.
So, Brewzers? Yeah?
We don't have to. We've met.
You said you wanted to talk.
Would it not better over a coffee?
Won't take long.
OK. So?
I'll do it. The DNA test.
But for two grand.
Wait.
Alright.
Why did you change your mind?
Called my mam. Asked her for a loan.
So I could maybe rent somewhere
for a couple of months,
get myself set up.
Get a job, you know.
She turned you down.
No.
Well, kind of. She said
we should go and stay with her.
In France?
That was the deal.
Me and Milo go to France.
Apparently we need looking after.
But you're not,
you're not going, right?
My mum's OK. She means well,
I know that,
and we get on alright,
as long as there's some distance
between us, so.
Two grand. Buys me time
and I figured
I might as well get something
from you lot.
Is that a problem?
No.
Cash.
I'll get it now.
We'll do the test today,
this morning. There's a clinic.
We'll all go. Milo too.
Is that a problem?
Milo's in school.
It'll only take an hour or so.
There, give the sample, back.
I'll just get a sample off him,
a strand of hair or whatever.
I'd rather he came with us.
So I know it's him.
So, what, I'd just go take a sample
from someone else
that shows James isn't the father?
Why would I do that?
Because you get to walk away
without any ties,
without any complications
and two grand.
Yeah, alright. Let's do it.
I can take him out for an hour.
I'll call you when I have the money.
Fine.
You going to this dance thing?
No. You?
No.
Yeah.
I wouldn't say
it's JJ's cup of tea, alright.
What's it got to do with him?
I don't want to go.
He can go if he wants.
Right, no, yeah, right,
I'm with you.
I wouldn't fancy it either.
Yeah. Anyway, I'll see you.
See you.
Alright?
Hey.
Zoe?
This, erm...
...attempted blackmail of yours.
Seeing as you turned down
my first offer, here's my new offer.
Nothing.
Well, that's pretty stupid.
No, you see, I think
you're being stupid
because you haven't
thought this through.
What's there to think?
You're doing something dodgy.
I found out about it.
And now you're going to pay
to keep me quiet.
And if I don't
you'll go to the guards.
Yeah. Money, by the end of the day.
I'm just trying to help you here,
you know.
Try and stop this
before you get in too deep.
Ooh (!) Do you think I'm scared?
You should be.
(SCOFFS) Of you?
Of JJ Nash.
See, you think
you're blackmailing me
but you're not.
You're blackmailing him.
And he doesn't bluff.
So... you really ought to
think about this.
So you say she's not a gold-digger
because you offered her the money
to do the test
and she turned you down.
But now she's doing it
for twice the money.
You want her to vanish off
to France?
Maybe she's lying.
Maybe her mother's in,
I don't know, Mullingar
and six months from now,
she turns up
looking for another two grand.
The money is to do the test.
She's not going to do another one
in six months.
So she finds another reason.
I don't think she's a gold-digger.
OK, fine. I'll tell you one thing.
She knows how to negotiate.
Twice the price
and you're paying for it.
We're paying for it.
Oh.
James is going to chip in, is he?
No, of course he's not.
I'll pay it all if you want.
No. It's a family expense
and it is expensive.
It's worth it.
To me.
Don't you want to know
if you have a grandchild?
(DOOR OPENING)
What are you doing here?
I'm getting building advice.
About what?
What it would cost
to put in a Jacuzzi.
A Jacuzzi?
Now you sound like your father.
He was complaining too.
I'm not complaining.
You'd use it for two weeks
and then it'll just be
an expensive bath with knobs on.
Yeah, but two weeks of bliss.
I can tell you what we do need.
Milk.
Well, put your clothes on
and go and get some.
Sorry it's the maid's day off.
Black coffee's fine.
Jacuzzi? Very smooth.
You too.
We were a good team.
We had our moments.
So we're not telling him?
Bad enough you getting at me.
I wasn't getting at you,
I was commenting.
Well, James can comment
when we get the results.
And what do you want
the results to be?
James is the father?
Or, as you put it,
you have a grandchild?
I don't know.
What do you want?
I want this woman to go away
and James to get on with his life
and that'll be a lot easier
if the child isn't his.
(MAKES STARTLED NOISE)
Ma, what are you doing?
Almost gave me a heart attack.
Plugging in my phone.
What's all this?
Oh, that's for the dance. I brought
them over from The Helping Hand.
It was the closest thing
to '20s style I could find.
Hey, Renee. Is the Lidl open yet?
No, not yet. I'm in training.
Couple of weeks.
So, are you ladies here
for some costumes for the dance?
No, I have a dress. Jacinta?
No, I'm not going.
You're not?
It's not my thing.
That's a pity.
You're not going?
I did my bit for the committee.
I'm not going to go prancing
round the place like a eejit.
No, I think you should go though.
Why is that?
What did we talk about before?
Making new friends,
putting in a bit of an effort.
I'll think about it.
Jacinta. Hello.
Oh, how are you?
I heard there were costumes
for the dance? Yeah.
Buy for ten, rent for five.
Great, thank you.
Er, my name is Melanie.
What?
Melanie.
Just, you were ignoring me, in case
you thought I was a stranger.
I wasn't ignoring you.
Still, I suppose it's better
than being rude like the other day.
I wasn't.
Oh, sorry, maybe that was
someone else. Who are you again?
So, a couple of days
should see us through.
And then what? We, er,
we take a break and then do another?
I always like to finish one thing
before talking about what's next.
Of course, yeah.
OK.
I'll be in touch.
Yeah.
Look, we might have a problem.
Zoe saw you handing me over
the cash.
So what?
She thinks something's going on.
Oh?
Look, it wasn't my fault.
I didn't even know
that she was there.
I tried to cool things down and...
and it all got a bit messy.
Why? There's nothing to cool down,
she doesn't know anything.
She wants money
or she's going to go to the guards.
You give her nothing.
Yeah, well, I tried that but don't
think that's going to work.
So what do we do?
You don't do anything.
You should have killed this
before it got this far.
But you couldn't even manage that.
So I'll deal with it.
How?
Efficiently.
(EMMA) So, coffee?
Just give me the money.
We should talk.
About what?
Well, Holly, take a wild guess.
So, what, you're not going to give
me the money now unless we talk?
The result won't be
until the end of the day.
If James is the father...
I'm sorry.
Well, then, I'm Milo's granny.
OMG, I'm an actual granny.
So shouldn't we talk about
what happens next?
About what we want to happen?
That's up to me.
Excuse me?
I decide what's going to happen.
My child.
My grandchild.
Oh, suddenly you're so sure
that James is the father.
I think Milo has Con's eyes.
Think he has my mum's eyes.
OK, we'll talk. But not today.
Just remember, whatever is
going to happen is my decision.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow, fine.
What's going on?
.
What is this?
Don't you touch me.
James.
Take it easy.
Are you paying her to pay her off?
She's scamming you.
It's for a DNA test.
What?
I'm paying her to take the test.
We don't need a test.
It's done.
I'm not the damn father.
You are.
What?
I was the only guy
you were sleeping with back then?
Holly? I don't need to stand here
and be called a liar, OK.
You're not going anywhere.
Are you going to stop me?
James.
Let her go.
You paid her.
I wanted to know the truth.
I told you the truth.
How can you be so naive?
Don't speak to your mother
like that. Why not?
When she's believing her
ahead of me?
James, I'm sorry.
Hey, Mum.
You know what?
Too little, too late.
As usual.
Have you any interest
in going to this dance?
Hell no.
If I wanted to go, would you come?
Hell yeah.
Do you want to?
Hell no.
Was that a test?
No. But you passed.
Sorry, look. Nora.
Jacinta is not really my cup of tea.
Well, it's just that
she's a bit awkward around people,
she's not used to it.
But it strikes me
she's a bit lonely.
Well, why don't you
take her to the dance then?
I don't want you to take her
to the dance.
I want you to ask her to the dance.
And the difference is?
So, she isn't going. She told me.
That's the difference.
So you ask her,
it's a nice gesture.
She isn't going
so you don't have to take her.
Hey.
Do you want to take a look
at these clothes?
You might find a costume
for the dance.
It's ten to buy, five to rent.
What's the catch?
What do you mean?
The trick, the joke, the insult.
There isn't one.
Why?
Because it's not worth my time.
I made you pay
for what you did to Fergal.
I'm satisfied. I won.
Er, Jacinta.
Hiya.
Are you going to the dance
with anyone?
No.
Would you like to go with me?
OK.
Great.
How's things with Gar?
(LAUGHING) What?
I told you.
Me and Gar were one night.
There are no "things."
So there's nothing
to let slip to Joan.
What are you talking about?
Why would I say that?
Look, Joan doesn't know
about me and Gar
because there's
nothing to know about.
Yeah, you just said that.
So if you happen to mention
anything to her,
all you'd be talking about
is a one-night stand.
And I don't think that
Joan would appreciate
hearing about her son's sex life.
Certainly not from an office junior.
If you're saying it to her,
who else are you saying it to?
I'm not saying it to anybody.
Good. Best say nothing.
I'm looking out for you here, OK?
Sounds like you're looking out
for yourself.
No. It's called
being discreet, Jess.
Something Joan appreciates.
Everything alright?
Yeah, fine.
Jess?
Everything's grand.
I was just in the Community Centre.
They have costumes for the dance.
Yeah, I was looking at them.
Find anything? No.
They weren't very good, were they?
Nothing stylish.
I might have to buy something.
Can't let the firm down.
Oh, is the firm paying for it?
(LAUGHS) Jess.
I'm glad you didn't get the ticket,
I'd be out of pocket.
Oh, no, I wouldn't expect
you to pay for it.
I would just find something.
I don't expect
Joan to pay for it either.
I'm sure I have a dress
I can just fix up
with some feathers or fringes
or whatever.
Actually, I think I have something
at home that might work.
Twenties style, kind of flapper?
I'll bring it in. Have a look.
Great. Thanks.
I hope it's not horrible.
That would be... awkward.
Hi, Ruth. It's Dad.
Listen, darling, I just want to say
I'm sorry for getting on your case
about staying over in Barcelona.
I just...
It's just that I miss you, you know?
And yes, of course you can stay over.
I want you to have
a really good time.
But, er, everything's well here,
erm, usual trucking along.
So, erm...
when you get this message,
if you get a chance,
you might give me a buzz back.
Tell me how things are going
and what's happening.
And, look, it's no hassle
if you can't, you're too busy.
(EXHALES) Yeah.
Well, erm... Oh.
Ruth?
I love you and I miss you.
Bye, darling.
(EXHALES SHAKILY)
My da wants to see you.
What about?
He didn't tell me.
He'll tell you.
Well, suppose I don't want
to see him?
This isn't about what you want.
When my da says meeting, you do it.
Station bar, now.
Hiya. Americano, please.
Are you alright?
Yeah, sorry. Hi. Er, fine.
What was it?
Americano.
Right.
What?
You told Nash?
He wants to see me.
What does that mean?
Just... just talk.
You know that for a fact?
Well, I'm sure he just doesn't want
any hassle, that's all.
What are you doing?
Getting my coat.
And where are you going?
What part of Nash wanting to see me
did you not understand?
You're going now?
He wants to see me now. Right now.
So I don't have a choice, do I?
(NORA) Come on, Leo.
Mightn't be so bad.
You swore to me.
Jacinta wouldn't accept.
Leo, be fair. She didn't swear.
And I did say she was lonely.
So there was always a chance
that she would agree.
You tell me that now.
I'm stuck with her now at the dance.
I am not bleeding lonely.
And I wouldn't dance with you if you
were the last man left on Earth.
What are you looking at?
So results by close of business.
What time does that mean?
Six.
I can't wait here till six,
I have a meeting to go to.
How long can you stay?
I don't know. Half an hour.
They said it might be earlier.
I was kind of half hoping
that the child was James's.
No. You were half hoping
you have a grandchild.
Yeah.
Why?
Have another go at raising a kid.
Sure you wouldn't be raising him.
Even better.
Hand him back after a few hours
but...
you know, be around,
part of his upbringing.
A good influence
instead of too little too late.
What James said was rubbish.
Was it?
He was angry, he was mouthing off.
He'd every right to be angry.
I did believe her over him.
Well, she's a good liar.
And I gave her all that money.
It'll be worth it
if it got rid of her.
Better value than a Jacuzzi.
(PHONE BUZZES)
Oh.
Test.
Hello?
Yes, that's me.
Yes, this morning.
Sorry, yes, just to be sure,
that means...
Right, OK. Thank you.
Bye.
Emma, for God's sake, come on.
Milo and I are a match.
James is the father.
OK, I, erm, I was doing
some business with JJ.
Cars?
No.
What then?
It doesn't matter.
The thing is, like I told you,
somebody saw us.
JJ handing me over cash.
Yeah?
Yeah. It was Zoe.
She got the idea
that something was happening.
Now she's looking for some money
to keep quiet.
You're kidding me. Zoe? How much?
That doesn't matter either.
But... look. I'm obviously
not going to pay
because you pay, you're admitting
there's something dodgy going on.
Wait, if you're not going to pay,
is she going to the guards?
She can't prove anything.
If she starts gabbing off,
guards are going to come
sniffing around.
JJ's not going to like that.
Maybe you'd be better off
paying her.
You don't want JJ knowing
anything about this.
What?
He knows.
She said it to him as well?
No, I did.
What did he say?
He said he'll deal with it.
And then he wanted to see Zoe
and that was over an hour ago.
I don't know what to do.
Should I call him,
tell him to back off? What?
How are you, lads?
Hiya.
JJ.
You alright, Zoe?
Yeah, fine.
Paul, can we have a word?
I'll leave you lads to it.
JJ.
Right.
So, me and Zoe had a chat.
She saw me giving you money
for that meal Steo had
and didn't pay for.
She misunderstood
what was going on. Yeah?
Yeah.
Sorry.
And, apparently,
you had a falling out
over the same thing
and it got out of hand.
Things were said, stupid things.
And Zoe got quite upset, didn't you?
Yeah.
So you should apologise to her.
Sorry.
And to show
there's no hard feelings,
I thought Zoe should have
a retainer.
A retainer?
She does deliveries for you.
No set routine, gives you a dig out.
Yeah.
So, a retainer.
A bonus for her being available.
A hundred euro a week. Sounds fair.
Yeah?
Paul?
Yeah.
Zoe?
Good. That's all settled then.
Now, Zoe. Cup of tea.
Start earning that retainer.
Sure.
Cheers.
Can we at least be civil?
Well, you weren't yesterday.
That was you,
telling me that I was being rude.
Well, you were.
What are you doing here?
You're Milo's father.
Our business arrangement.
That stuff with Zoe earlier...
That's all done with.
And actually, so are we.
Sorry?
My name is Gareth.
I don't believe we've had the
pleasure of meeting.
And your name is?
Subtitles by Iyuno